

GRAPHIC DESIGNER & ILLUSTRATOR

PROFICIENCY

- Graphic Design
- Motion Graphics
- Illustration
- UI/UX Design
- Web and Interactive Design
- Branding and Style Guides

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Illustrator HTML
- Photoshop
- CSS
- After Effects
- Adobe XD
- JavaScript JQuery

- Figma
- PHP
- InDesign
- MySQL
- Sketch
- WordPress

SUMMARY

Passionate graphic designer and Illustrator. Excellent at creating lively, colorful design and illustrations, with extensive knowledge and experience in Adobe Creative Cloud Suite as well as prototyping tools such as Figma, Adobe XD, and Sketch.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer and Illustrator

AAE Corporation

Wyandanch, NY 2023 - present

- Created graphics and illustrations for brand promotions, lists of expanses and infographics for contractors.
- Put together brand style guides and marketing materials.
- Created graphic instructions for brand promotions and Indiegogo campaigns.

Graphic Designer and Brand Strategist

Kinetics Technology Corp.

Taipei, Taiwan 2021 - 2022

- Helped design company logo and style guides.
- Provided guidance and support to the team throughout the development process, ensuring that the brand's visual elements were consistent and effective across all media.

Executive of Art and Design

National Taiwan Normal University - Department of Physics

Taipei, Taiwan 2012 - 2014

- Designed department uniforms.
- Designed posters and digital advertisements for events and activities.

EDUCATION

MA in Interaction & UI/UX Design Academy of Art University (GPA 3.83/4.00)

San Francisco, CA 2021 - 2023